{
    "id": "6c4b7397d94f47d38975325d22ea3bfc",
    "title": "Grammar Check",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "Which of the following is the plural form of young one?",
            "description": "There are no apostrophes in plural nouns.",
            "answers": [
                "young ones",
                "young one's",
                "young ones'"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "dbc3706cf235450e81b5383d508a5c86"
        },
        {
            "question": "Which of the following sentences is grammatically correct?",
            "description": "We cannot use past time expressions with the present perfect tense.",
            "answers": [
                "I have seen him yesterday.",
                "I saw him yesterday."
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "6af65b469e7f4da384d871f452dd320d"
        },
        {
            "question": "The simple present tense can be used to talk about future.",
            "description": "The simple present tense can be used to talk about future events that are part of a time table.",
            "answers": [
                "True",
                "False"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "42b83443988d4ca8a68495e006498a6b"
        },
        {
            "question": "The negative form of will is ............................",
            "description": "In the case of auxiliary verbs, questions and negatives are made without do.",
            "answers": [
                "will not",
                "don't will",
                "doesn't will"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "6ff83d40e5e2422fa429e765a4935787"
        },
        {
            "question": "Which of the following sentences is grammatically correct?",
            "description": "Look is a copular verb we use adjectives to modify copular verbs.",
            "answers": [
                "She looked happy",
                "She looked happily",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "23dee608c2394f9cb7aa37f6e3d9918d"
        },
        {
            "question": "Can you lend me ................................ of butter?",
            "description": "Pound is a singular countable noun we need an article or another determiner with singular countable nouns.",
            "answers": [
                "pound",
                "a pound",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "a7eed95635054a64bfd4fcdbe039e86b"
        },
        {
            "question": "We have got enough money to buy a car. Here enough is an ...............................",
            "description": "When enough modifies a noun, it is an adjective.",
            "answers": [
                "adjective",
                "adverb"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "5134834e181c4f65989a2e45fc929213"
        },
        {
            "question": "She is old enough to know better. Here enough is an ......................................",
            "description": "When enough modifies an adjective, it is an adverb.",
            "answers": [
                "adjective",
                "adverb"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "5755ba932d6d4f829cd29e8466a19a6b"
        },
        {
            "question": "I love ................................ types of cars.",
            "description": "We use these and those with plural nouns.",
            "answers": [
                "these",
                "this",
                "that"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "1f3c27acac2849a395c8c06349f084f9"
        },
        {
            "question": "There are no secrets between ....................................",
            "description": "We use object pronouns after a preposition.",
            "answers": [
                "us",
                "we"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "26fdd3529b2f43ebbb7ac847bae8460a"
        },
        {
            "question": "Which of the following is not a form of be?",
            "description": "The forms of be are: is, am, are, was and were.",
            "answers": [
                "are",
                "were",
                "am",
                "has"
            ],
            "correct": 3,
            "id": "f3498f14e4e74b3f8d049d1b54495bd8"
        },
        {
            "question": "My brother loves ...........................................",
            "description": "We do not normally use articles with plural nouns when we are talking about things in general.",
            "answers": [
                "dogs",
                "the dogs",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "15d4f689a1904edc914d341156bd1c6c"
        }
    ]
}